<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--Generated by crowdin.com-->
<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2014 AChep@xda <artemchep@gmail.com>
  ~
  ~ This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
  ~ modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License
  ~ as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2
  ~ of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
  ~
  ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
  ~ but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
  ~ MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
  ~ GNU General Public License for more details.
  ~
  ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
  ~ along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
  ~ Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston,
  ~ MA  02110-1301, USA.
  -->
<resources>
  <string name="close">Đóng</string>
  <string name="about_action">Thông tin</string>
  <string name="about_message"><![CDATA[         Bản quyền năm 2013-2014 <a href="https://plus.google.com/+АртёмЧепурной"> của Artem Chepurnoy</a>. Tất cả các quyền được bảo hộ. <br/>         <br/> Cảm ơn mã nguồn của các công cụ sau: %1$s và tất cả những ai <a href="http://translate.acdisplay.org"> đã giúp với bản dịch</a> hoặc <a href="https://plus.google.com/102696863054832206920/posts/7wi3WfWGSfH"> tặng cho tôi</a>.     
]]></string>
  <string name="help">Trợ giúp</string>
  <string name="help_faq">Các câu hỏi thường gặp</string>
  <string name="news_message"><![CDATA[
         Chào mừng đến với phiên bản mới của AcDisplay!
         Bản cập nhật này đem lại thiết kế hoàn toàn mới và độc đáo với rất nhiều khả năng mới.
         Thiết kế hơn được sắp xếp hợp lý hơn và cung cấp cho bạn trải nghiệm tốt nhất có thể!<br/>
         <br/>
         <b>Một chạm cho tất cả hành động.</b><br/>
         Mở khóa điện thoại, kiểm tra các thông báo hoặc thực hiện một hành động có thể được thực hiện chỉ với một thao tác đơn giản. <br/>
         <br/>
         <b>Mở khóa ở bất cứ đâu và ở tất mọi nơi.</b><br/>
         Trượt bất cứ nơi nào trên các không gian trống để mở khóa.
]]></string>
  <string name="speech_message"><![CDATA[
        Hello,<br/>
        First of all I want to thank you for the amount of downloads and high ratings on Play Store.
        Huge progress has been made in AcDisplay and a this could not have been done without the community. That is why AcDisplay is <a href="https://www.github.com/AChep/AcDisplay">open</a> for everyone. But I need some help from you.<br/>
        This is my last school year and I would like to buy a notebook for future studies and to bring the world awesome software wherever I may be.
        I would highly appreciate your help with it.
    ]]></string>
</resources>
